Tēlemachos Alaveras Papers and Nea Poreia Archives, 1989-2010: Finding Aid C1408
Manuscripts Division
- Series 1: Tēlemachos Alaveras Papers, 1889-2010; 47 boxes; 2 items
  - Subseries 1G: Writings by Others, 1920-2010; 11 boxes
    - Talks; Articles; Reviews; Translations; Essays; Dissertation on Alaveras's Works, 1955-2010; 3 boxes
      - Mauridēs, Panagiōtēs. "Tēlemachos Alaveras: hē gnōrimia, hē philia, hē apōleia", 2010 December 11; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 3)
        Includes photocopies of Maurides's autograph manuscripts of his talk given at the Hetairia Logotechnōn Thessalonikēs [The Literary Society of Thessalonikē].
      - Pantelia, Stylianē. "Hē peripeteia tou taxidiou, peripeteia tēs graphēs", 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 4)
        Includes an autograph and a typescript, as well as magazine clippings of a review based on Alavera's book S'eutheia grammē.
      - Samaras, Margaritēs N. & Samara, Zōē. "Hē pezographia sēmera: oikonomikes domes kai aphēgēmatikē phantasia", 2003; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 5)
        Included also are copies of the following essays by Zōe Samara: "Tēlemachos Alaveras: ta mystēria tes aphēgēsēs"; and "Hē poiētike tēs mythoplasias sto ergo tou Tēlemachou Alavera."
      - Sphakianakēs, Giannēs G., undated; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 6)
        Includes two reviews of Alaveras's books To rologi and Ho hodostrōtēras written by Sphakianakēs.
      - Stergiopoulos, Kōstas. "Ho Tēlemachos Alaveras kai hē paradosē tēs Thessalonikēs", 1987 March 12; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 7)
        Includes autograph manuscripts and typescripts of Stergiopoulos's talk given at the Vaphopouleio Cultural Center in Thessalonikē (Greece). There is also an essay published in the literary magazine K.
      - Tsakōnas, Dēmētrēs, undated; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 8)
        Includes autograph manuscripts and typescripts of a criticism on Alaveras's work.
      - Vassēs, Kōnstantinos. "Tēlemachos Alaveras. Anazētōntas tēn tautotēta tēs synchronēs pezographias." Article, undated; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Votaniatēs, Agis. "Apo to prosōpo stēn aphormē tou prosōpou", 1997 January 24; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 10)
        Includes photocopies of the autograph manuscript of Votaniatēs's talk at Vaphopouleio Cultural Center, as well as a copy of the published talk in the literary magazine Hē Lexē, 138 (March-April 1997).
      - Miscellaneous Essays; Reviews; Talks, 1952-2010; 3 folders (Box 37, Folder 11-13)
        Consists of autograph manuscripts of reviews of Alaveras's books: Ho hodostrotēras by S.I. Vasileiadēs, T'agrimia tou allou dasous, and To rologi by Bampēs Nintas, K.G. Kosmas, and Giōrgos Delios; typescripts of a radio program by Giannēs Karalēs broadcast on the Nation Broadcasting Corporation-Radio of Patras in 1952. Included also are photocopies of essays or reviews of Alaveras's books published in Greek literary magazines by several Greek writers; a talk with the title "To periodiko Nea Poreia kai ho Tēlemachos Alaveras" given on December 11, 2010 at the Hetairia Logotechnōn Thessalonikēs [The Literary Society of Thessalonikē] by an unidentified speaker. There is also a second talk probably given during the same event (undated); and a college research paper.
      - Translations, 1955-2001; 2 folders (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
        Includes autograph manuscripts and photocopies of typescripts with handwritten corrections of Alaveras's work T'agrimia tou allou dasous [Les bêtes sauvages de l'autre forêt] translated into French by Annie Koutokoi-Chatzipoulidou; typescripts of a German translation; photocopies of printed translations into German of the works "Paraisthēseis" and "Mia mera akomē"; "La meta della luna" in Italian published in L'Argime Letterario, Nuova Serie (Dicembre 1971); "Un giorno ancora" published in Alla Bottega, Anno X, no. 2 (Marzo-Aprile 1972); "Pro-po" ["Fussballtoto"] in German translation by W. Ekschmitt; "Wahnvorstellungen" translated by Judith Eickler; and translations in Cyrillic.
      - Bibliography of Book Reviews, 2006-2008; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 3)
        Includes notes, typescripts and autograph manuscripts by Alaveras; lists of his bibliography and published bookreviews of his works; a press release; and two CDs.
  - Subseries 1H: Photographs, 1923-2006; 2 boxes
    This subseries includes photographs of Tēlemachos and Roula Alaveras; portraits of Alaveras; Alaveras with his friends, colleagues, politicians, relatives, and acquaintances participating in several events: award ceremonies; meetings with old classmates; taks; literary symposia; book signings; book presentations; exhibitions; events organized by Roula Alavera; the opening ceremony of the Vaphopouleion Cultural Center; and others. There are also portraits of several Greek writers or poets, such as Giannēs Ritsos (included a copy of a photograph of Ritsos with Manos Katrakes in the exile); Dēmētrēs Dēmou; Kōstas Varnalēs; Giōrgēs Kotsiras; Paulos Papasiōpēs; Helenē Vakalo; Alkiviadēs Giannopoulos; Chrēstos Dalias; Anastasēs Vistōnitēs; Michales Meraklēs; Mēnas Dēmakēs; Paulos Spandōnidēs; Giannēs Sphakianakēs; Giōrgos Themelēs; and many others, as well as politicians.
    This subseries has been arranged in a chronological order except the first folder.
    - Portraits of Tēlemachos and Roula Alaveras, 1930-2002; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Book Presentations; Talks; Conferences; Literary Meetings; Miscellaneous, 1923-1984; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Portraits of Greek Literary Figures, 1936-1982; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Award Ceremonies; Conferences; Lectures, 1987-1990; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - National Chronicle-Witness Award Ceremony; High School Students Event, 1991; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Opening Ceremony of Vaphopouleio Pneumatiko Kentro, 1992; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Nea Poreia Event; Conference; Meeting, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Includes photographs of Nea Poreia event at Vaphopouleio Pneumatiko Kentro (Vaphopouleion Cultural Center); the International Conference Kōstē Palama; a meeting with Alaveras's classmates; and a student event with the Hetaireia Logotechnōn Thessalonikēs.
    - Lecture with Giōrgos Kaphtantzēs, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Includes photographs of the lecture with Kaphtantzēs; a literary event for Takes Varvitsiōtēs; and an award ceremony.
    - Literary Event in Perivoli, Grevena, 1997; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Alaveras' Book Presentation and Signing; Trips; Hetaireia Logotechnōn Thessalonikēs [Thessalonikē Writer's Association], 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Logotechniko Vraveio Phreiderikou Mathious; Hetairia Logotechnōn Thessalonikēs [Thessalonikē Writer's Association], 2001-2003; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Stoa tou Vivliou Event; Public Library of Thessalonikē Event, 2005-2006; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Undated, 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1I: Audio-Visual Material; Designs, 1979-2009; 3 boxes
    This subseries consists of audio-visual material containing information about Alaveras's books, Nea Poreia publications, cultural events, radio programs, and some book designs.
    This subsereis has been organized by type of material.
    - Video Tapes, 1997-2005; 1 box (Box 40)
    - CDs; Floppy Disks; and Cassetes, 1995-2009; 1 box (Box 41)
    - Journal and Book Designs, 1979-1994; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1J: Printed Material, 1889-2009; 5 boxes
    Consists of clippings of newspapers and literary magazines regarding literary activities in Thessalonikē, Greece.
    This subseries has been organized in a chronological order. At the end of the subseries there is a folder with memorabilia.
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1913-2009; 3 boxes
      This group has been organizaed in a chronological order.
      Includes clippings of several Greek, American, and French newspapers, which contain articles on literary topics written by Tēlemachos Alaveras and others.
      - On Alaveras's Books, 1952-2007; 2 boxes
        Consists of reviews about Alavera's works and awards. There are also articles or stories published in series. This group has been organized in an alphabetical order.
        - Akriva gousta hē kyria, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Ap'aphormē, 1977-1986; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 3)
          Includes clippings regarding book reviews and the award that Alaveras received.
        - Diēgēmatographoi tēs Thessalonikēs, 1889-1989; 2 folders (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
          Includes offprints and issues of literary magazines. Included are: the article "Ta prōta logotechnika periodika tēs Thessalonikēs (1921-1924)" by Dinos Christianopoulos published in Diagōnios, 1975; the essay "Hellēnikos logotechnikos periodikos typos (1974-1984)" by Antōnēs Kalphas dated 1985; Diavazō, 747 (1986); Aristotelēs 10 (May 15, 1889); Logotechniko deltio, 37 (August 1970); Exōstēs, 76 (December 22, 1989); Pyrsos tōn apophoitōn tou Peiramatikou, 3 (December 1953); Neanikē skepsē, 1 (December 1, 1929); Augē, 3 (1922); and clippings of Greek newspapers with reviews of Alaveras's book.
        - Gōnies kai opseis, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Hodostrōtēras, 1964-1988; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
          Includes clippings of local newspapers and literary magazines; Dōdekatē hōra, 8; Pneumatikē Kypros, 46-47 (July-August 1964); and Euvoikos logos, 71-73 (January-March 1964).
        - Hōs kyliomenos tapēs, 1999; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Me ton Barmpalia, 1999-2001; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
        - S'eutheia grammē, 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
          Includes clippings regarding bookreviews and the ceremony of the awards.
        - Sēmeiōseis, 1969-2002; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - T'agrimia tou allou dasous, 1952-1999; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
          Includes clippings of Greek newspapers with reviews and publication announcements of the book.
        - To rologi, 1957-1962; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Awards, 1987-2007; 1 box
        - Ourane Foundation Academy of Athens Award, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - Logotechnika Vraveia 1998, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
          Includes a printed invitation of the magazine Diavazō and Greek newspaper clippings.
        - Kratika Logotechnika Vraveia 2006-2007 [State Literary Awards 2006-2007], 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
          Includes newspaper clippings, the poster, and the booklet of the event.
      - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1913-1966; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Literary Criticism on Alaveras's Works, 1952-2006; 2 folders (Box 43, Folder 8-9)
      - Hellēnikos vorras, 1965-1982; 2 folders (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
        Includes clippings of the local newspaper Hellēnikos vorras where Alaveras was an editor and regular columnist signing as "Ho Synergatēs A."
      - Hesperinē hōra, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 3)
        Includes clippings of the local newspaper Hesperinē hōra where Alaveras was an editor and regular columnist signing as "Ho Synergatēs A."
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1973; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1974-2009; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - 4ē Diethnēs Ekthesē Vivliou Thessalonikēs, 2007; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - On Alaveras's Death, 2007; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Magazines and Magazine Clippings, 1889-2003; 4 folders (Box 45, Folder 1-4)
      Includes originals and photocopies, as well as clippings of several literary magazines, which according to Roula Alavera's note on the discarded envelope they were used as references for Tēlemachos Alaveras's study on the literary journals of Thessalonikē (see: "Ta logotechnika periodika tēs Thessalonikēs"). Included are: Aristotelēs, 1 (January 1889); Phōnē tēs proodou, 90 (October 1979); Makedonikē zōē, 172 (September 1980); Vivliothēkē, 118 (September 1, 2000) and 240 (January 24, 2003); 6ē Hēmera, 49 (February 12-13, 2000); Mēnes, (January-February and March-April 1962); Ta phoitētika grammata, 1 (March 1955); 2 (April 1955); and 3 (May-June 1953); Eumenēs, March and April 1959; and Kouinta, 6 (May 1996).
    - Book Covers, undated; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Tour Guides and Maps of France and Vienna (Austria), 1992; 2 folders (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
      Includes phone cards, museum tickets and catalogs, guide books, and maps of France, and one map of Vienna.
    - Posters, 1986-2008; 1 box (Box 46)
- Series 2: Nea Poreia Archives, 1918-2009; 43 boxes
  This series consists of autograph manuscripts and typescripts of published and unpublished works by several Greek writers or poets, including Tēlemachos Alaveras.
  This series has been organized into five subseries: A. Nea Poreia Journal; B. Nea Poreia Publications; C. Associations-Organizations; D. Miscellaneous Documents: Legal; Financial; Contact Information; Press; Memorabilia; and E. Printed Material.
  - Subseries 2A: Nea Poreia Journal, 1957-2009; 19 boxes
    Includes originals and copies of autograph manuscripts and typescripts, as well as page proofs with autograph manuscript annotations of works by several modern Greek poets and writers published in the issues of the literary magazine Nea Poreia. There are also a few photographs (color and black-and-white); floppy disks; and clippings of Greek newspapers.
    They have been arranged in a chronological order.
    - Nea Poreia, 31, 1957; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Published in September 1957.
    - Nea Poreia, 146-147, 1967; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
      Published in April-May 1967.
    - Nea Poreia, 148-149, 1967; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Published in June-July 1967. Includes page proofs that they have been censored by the Government Presidency, General Administration of Press (Thessalonikē).
    - Nea Poreia, 150-151, 1967; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Published in August-September 1967. Includes page proofs that they have been censored by the Government Presidency, General Administration of Press (Thessalonikē).
    - Nea Poreia, 152-153, 1967; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
      Published in October-November 1967. Includes page proofs that they have been censored by the Government Presidency, General Administration of Press (Thessalonikē) and printed photocopies.
    - Nea Poreia, 154, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      Published in December 1967. Includes page proofs that they have been censored by the Government Presidency, General Administration of Press (Thessalonikē) on January 29, 1968.
    - Nea Poreia, 155-157, 1968; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      Published in January-June 1968. Includes page proofs that they have been cesnsored; there are also a printed photocopy of the issue.
    - Nea poreia, 158-159, 1968; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Published in April-May 1968. Includes page proofs that they have been censored and photocopies.
    - Nea Poreia, 160-161, 1968; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 9)
      Published in June-August 1968. Includes page proofs that have been censored.
    - Nea Poreia, 167-169, 1969; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 10)
      Published in January-March 1969. Includes page proofs that they have been cesnsored.
    - Nea Poreia, 170-171, 1969; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 11)
      Published in April-May 1969. Includes page proofs that they have been censored.
    - Nea Poreia, 172-174, 1969; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 12)
      Published in June-August 1969. Includes page proofs that they have been censored.
    - Nea Poreia, 243-246, 1975 May -August; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 13)
      Published in May -August 1975. Includes page proofs of the "Euretēria Neas Poreias 1965-1974."
    - Nea Poreia, 296-298, undated; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 14)
      Published in October-December 1979. Includes autograph manuscript drafts of the short story "Hē syneleusē" by Alkiviadēs Giannopoulos.
    - Nea Poreia, "Ta teleutaia eikosipente chronia tēs neohellēnikēs logotechnias." Special issue, 1973-1981; 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 15-16)
      Published in April 1981. Includes autograph manuscripts; carbon copies of typescripts; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, "Ta teleutaia eikosipente chronia tēs neohellēnikēs logotechnias." Special issue, 1973-1981; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Nea Poreia, 311-313, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Published in January-December 1981. Includes some autograph manuscripts of a translation by Takēs Varvitsiōtes.
    - Nea Poreia, 321-322, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Published in November-December 1981. Includes a typescript by Tolēs Nikēphorou.
    - Nea Poreia, 326-329, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Published in April-July 1982. Includes autograph manuscripts; carbon copies of typescripts; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 330-332, 1978-1982; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Published in August-October 1982. Includes typescripts and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 338-340, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Published in April-June 1983. Includes autograph manuscripts and typescripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 341-344, 1983; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Published in July-October 1983. Includes autograph manuscripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 345-346, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Published in November-December 1983. Includes an autograph manuscript by Giorgēs Manousakēs.
    - Nea Poreia, 347-349, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 9)
      Published in January-March 1984. Includes autograph manuscripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 350-352, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Published in April-June 1984. Includes an autograph manuscript, carbon typescripts, and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 353-356, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Published in July-October 1984. Includes typescripts with autograph corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 357-358, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 12)
      Published in November-December 1984. Includes autograph manuscripts and typescripts.
    - Nea Poreia. "To provlēma tēs kritikēs." Special issue, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 49, Folder 13-14)
      Published in 1985. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts, typescripts, and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia. "To provlēma tēs kritikēs." Special issue, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
    - Nea Poreia, 359-361, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Published in January-March 1985. Includes typescripts with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 362-365, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Publisehd in April-July 1985. Includes some autograph and typed manuscripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 366-368, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Published in August-October 1985. Includes autograph manuscripts; originals and photocopies of typescripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 369-370, 1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Published in November-December 1985. Includes autograph and typed manuscripts, as well as page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 371-373, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 7)
      Published in January-March 1986. Includes autograph manuscripts; page proofs with handwritten corrections; and typescripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 374-376, 1983-1986; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Published in April-June 1986. Includes autograph manuscripts; page proofs with handwritten corrections; and typescripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 377-380, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 9)
      Published in July-October 1986. Includes autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 381-382, 1986; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 10)
      Published in November-December 1986. Includes autograph manuscripts; carbon typescripts; and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 383-385, 1986; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 11)
      Published in January-March 1987. Includes autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 386-388, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 12)
      Published in April-June 1987. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph and typed manuscripts; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 389-392, 1987; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Published in July-October 1987. Includes autograph manuscripts; typescripts with handwritten corrections; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 393-394, undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Published in November-December 1987. Includes autograph manuscripts; typescripts and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 395-397, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Published in January-March 1988. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts and typescripts, as well as page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 398-400, undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 4)
      Published in April-June 1988. Includes some autograph manuscript drafts and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, Logotechnia tēs Thessalonikēs, Special edition, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
      Published in June 1988.
    - Nea Poreia, 401-404, 1988; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 7)
      Published in July-October 1988. Includes autograph manuscripts; photocopies of typescripts; and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 405-406, 1988; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 8)
      Published in November-December 1988. Includes autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 407-409, 1989; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Published in January-March 1989. Includes autograph manuscripts; carbon copies; and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 410-412, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Published in April-June 1989. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 413-415, 1989; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Published in July-September 1989. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs with handwritten corrections.
    - Nea Poreia, 416-418, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Published in October-December 1989. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs with handwritten annotations.
    - Nea Poreia, 419-421, 1979-1990; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 5)
      Published in January-March 1990. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts; page proofs; and carbon typescripts with handwritten annotations.
    - Nea Poreia, 422-424, 1990; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Published in April-June 1990. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs with handwritten annotations.
    - Nea Poreia, 425-428, 1990; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 7)
      Published in July-October 1990. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscript drafts; photocopies of typescripts; and page proofs with handwritten annotations.
    - Nea Poreia, 429-430, 1990; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 8)
      Published in November-December 1990. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs.
    - Nea Poreia, 431-433, 1991; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Published in January-March 1991. Includes originals and photocopies of autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs with handwritten annotations.
    - Nea Poreia, 434-437, 1991; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Published in April-July 1991. Includes page poofs with autograph manuscript annotations; autograph manuscripts; and typescripts.
    - Nea Poreia, 438-440, 1991; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Published in August-October 1991. Includes autograph manuscripts; typescripts; and page proofs with autograph manuscript annotations.
    - Nea Poreia, 441-442, 1991; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 4)